ELLIZEU RODRIGUES SENA

Electronics and Computer Engineer

About Me

Passionate developer eager for new challenges, I have worked on technology projects across two continents (Europe and America). Strong knowledge of agile methodology and excel in teamwork. Entrepreneurial spirit!

- ***** 1999/11/21
- **)** +55 (21) 97261-6385
- ✓ ellizeurs@hotmail.com
- () /ellizeurs
- in /ellizeurs
- Rio de Janeiro

Skills

- C++, C, Python, Bash, PHP, Javascript, JQuery, React, Node, C#, Java, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MatLab
- 🎤 🗗 EX, HTML, CSS
- A {MS, Libre, GSuite} Office
- Linux, Windows
- VsCode
- 🚣 Scrum, DevOps

Languages

- Portuguese (C2)
- A ≠ English (C1)
- A≢ Spanish (B2)

<i>(</i>)[\neg	\frown	Γ I \	/F

My objective is to work in the field of electronics and computer engineering, focusing on computing, data science, web development, and machine learning.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FundX Academy

Back End Developer | Tech Leader, Full-time MAY 2022 - OCT 2022

Empresa de Pesquisa Energética

Data Scientist, Part-time

OCT 2021 - OCT 2023

Universinagem

Back-End Developer, Full-time

OCT 2019 -

Minerva Rockets

Innovation Engineer, Part-time

OCT 2019 - MAR 2022

EDUCATION

Universidade Federal do Rio de Janeiro (Bachelor's Degree)

RIO DE JANEIRO, RJ 2017 – Electronics and Computer Engineering

FAETEC RJ - E.T.E. João Luiz do Nascimento (High School and Technical Education)

Nova Iguaçu, RJ 2014 - 2016 Electronics Technician